Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1929; UP056.001.020.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 27, 1929; UP056.001.020.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.83 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 10, 1929; UP056.001.020.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.11 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 17, 1929; UP056.001.020.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.61 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1929; UP056.001.020.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.76 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1929; UP056.001.020.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.38 Megabytes (Box 20)
    Alumnae Dramatic Club presents 'Love in a Mist'; Lucien P. Adams (1930). Photo - Baseball Player.; [Administration] College adopts rule to punish delinquents in payment of bills. p. 1
  - Tufts Weekly, May 8, 1929; UP056.001.020.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.71 Megabytes (Box 20)
    [Administration] College adopts rule to punish delinquents in payment of bills. p. 1
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1929; UP056.001.020.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.51 Megabytes (Box 20)
    Alumnae Dramatic Club presents 'Love in a Mist'
  - Tufts Weekly, May 22, 1929; UP056.001.020.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.43 Megabytes (Box 20)
    Alumnae Dramatic Club presents 'Love in a Mist'; [American association of University professors] Dr. Joseph Mayer to spend a year in charge of permanent office at Washington
  - Tufts Weekly, May 29, 1929; UP056.001.020.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.02 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 19, 1929; UP056.001.020.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.05 Megabytes (Box 20)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 25, 1929; UP056.001.021.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.76 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 2, 1929; UP056.001.021.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.89 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 9, 1929; UP056.001.021.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.67 Megabytes (Box 21)
    All Around Club; [Alumnae Dramatic Club] presents 'You and I' on Homecoming; [Alumni] Interest in undergraduates fostered
  - Tufts Weekly, October 16, 1929; UP056.001.021.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.40 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 23, 1929; UP056.001.021.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.50 Megabytes (Box 21)
    All Around Club; [Alumnae Dramatic Club] presents 'You and I' on Homecoming
  - Tufts Weekly, October 30, 1929; UP056.001.021.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.76 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 6, 1929; UP056.001.021.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.93 Megabytes (Box 21)
    Academic Honors, 1921-1932, p. 6. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 13, 1929; UP056.001.021.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 18.27 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 20, 1929; UP056.001.021.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.19 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 27, 1929; UP056.001.021.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.13 Megabytes (Box 21)
    Academic Honors, 1921-1932, pp. 1,2,4.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 4, 1929; UP056.001.021.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.52 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 11, 1929; UP056.001.021.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.09 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 18, 1929; UP056.001.021.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.04 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 8, 1930; UP056.001.021.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.23 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 15, 1930; UP056.001.021.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.58 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 5, 1930; UP056.001.021.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.30 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 12, 1930; UP056.001.021.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.89 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 19, 1930; UP056.001.021.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.34 Megabytes (Box 21)
    [American institute of Electrical Engineers] Plans for Tufts branch; Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega; [Alumnae Hall] plans announced, to be named for Ruth Capen Farmer
  - Tufts Weekly, February 26, 1930; UP056.001.021.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.81 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 5, 1930; UP056.001.021.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.34 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 12, 1930; UP056.001.021.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.22 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 19, 1930; UP056.001.021.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.83 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 26, 1930; UP056.001.021.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.15 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 9, 1930; UP056.001.021.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.14 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 16, 1930; UP056.001.021.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.68 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 23, 1930; UP056.001.021.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.33 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 30, 1930; UP056.001.021.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.00 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 7, 1930; UP056.001.021.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.55 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 14, 1930; UP056.001.021.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.65 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 21, 1930; UP056.001.021.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.35 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 28, 1930; UP056.001.021.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.79 Megabytes (Box 21)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 18, 1930; UP056.001.021.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.91 Megabytes (Box 21)
    commencement issue
  - Tufts Weekly, September 24, 1930; UP056.001.022.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.98 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1930; UP056.001.022.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.55 Megabytes (Box 22)
    All Around Club; [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising
  - Tufts Weekly, October 8, 1930; UP056.001.022.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.07 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 15, 1930; UP056.001.022.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.34 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 22, 1930; UP056.001.022.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.26 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 29, 1930; UP056.001.022.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.08 Megabytes (Box 22)
    [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising
  - Tufts Weekly, November 5, 1930; UP056.001.022.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.00 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1930; UP056.001.022.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.35 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1930; UP056.001.022.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.69 Megabytes (Box 22)
    Academic Honors, 1921-1932, pp. 1,5-6. All Around Club; [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1930; UP056.001.022.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.51 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 10, 1930; UP056.001.022.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.05 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1930; UP056.001.022.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.45 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 7, 1931; UP056.001.022.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.44 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1931; UP056.001.022.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.27 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 21, 1931; UP056.001.022.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.74 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 11, 1931; UP056.001.022.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.52 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1931; UP056.001.022.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.98 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25, 1931; UP056.001.022.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.02 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1931; UP056.001.022.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.98 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1931; UP056.001.022.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.15 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1931; UP056.001.022.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.58 Megabytes (Box 22)
    Alpha Tau Omega; [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1931; UP056.001.022.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.12 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 8, 1931; UP056.001.022.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.80 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 15, 1931; UP056.001.022.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.00 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 22, 1931; UP056.001.022.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.70 Megabytes (Box 22)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1931; UP056.001.022.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.36 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1931; UP056.001.022.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.65 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1931; UP056.001.022.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.19 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1931; UP056.001.022.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.81 Megabytes (Box 22)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 27, 1931; UP056.001.022.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.21 Megabytes (Box 22)
    [Alpha Kappa Kappa] Formerly Delta Phi Sigma.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 17, 1931; UP056.001.022.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.35 Megabytes (Box 22)
    Commencement Issue; [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising; Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, September 23, 1931; UP056.001.023.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.04 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 30, 1931; UP056.001.023.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.04 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1931; UP056.001.023.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.91 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 14, 1931; UP056.001.023.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.05 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1931; UP056.001.023.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.39 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1931; UP056.001.023.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.26 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1931; UP056.001.023.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.03 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 11, 1931; UP056.001.023.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.71 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1931; UP056.001.023.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.15 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 25, 1931; UP056.001.023.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.66 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1931; UP056.001.023.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.46 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1931; UP056.001.023.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.46 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1931; UP056.001.023.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.00 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 6, 1932; UP056.001.023.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.33 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1932; UP056.001.023.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.96 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 20, 1932; UP056.001.023.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.13 Megabytes (Box 23)
    Academic Honors p. 1; [Alumnae Hall] Fundraising
  - Tufts Weekly, Februray 10, 1932; UP056.001.023.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.04 Megabytes (Box 23)
    Academic Honors pp. 1,3.
  - Tufts Weekly, Februray 17, 1932; UP056.001.023.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.82 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, Februray 24, 1932; UP056.001.023.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.71 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 2, 1932; UP056.001.023.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.49 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 9, 1932; UP056.001.023.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.79 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 16, 1932; UP056.001.023.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.94 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 23, 1932; UP056.001.023.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 23)
    All Around Club. Frederick C. Allen (1913) Elected president of Tufts Club of Boston.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 6, 1932; UP056.001.023.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.53 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 13, 1932; UP056.001.023.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.22 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 20, 1932; UP056.001.023.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.80 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 27, 1932; UP056.001.023.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.48 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 4, 1932; UP056.001.023.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.55 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 11, 1932; UP056.001.023.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.85 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 18, 1932; UP056.001.023.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.75 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 25, 1932; UP056.001.023.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.78 Megabytes (Box 23)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 15, 1932; UP056.001.023.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.27 Megabytes (Box 23)
    Alumni association officers elected; Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, September 28, 1932; UP056.001.024.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.95 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1932; UP056.001.024.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.19 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 12, 1932; UP056.001.024.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.11 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1932; UP056.001.024.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.51 Megabytes (Box 24)
    Academic Honors, 1921-1932, pp. 1,2.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1932; UP056.001.024.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.02 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1932; UP056.001.024.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.99 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1932; UP056.001.024.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.76 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 16, 1932; UP056.001.024.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.17 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 23, 1932; UP056.001.024.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.38 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 30, 1932; UP056.001.024.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.18 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1932; UP056.001.024.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.87 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1932; UP056.001.024.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.83 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 18, 1933; UP056.001.024.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.03 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 25 1933, UP056.001.024.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.79 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1933; UP056.001.024.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.38 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 22, 1933; UP056.001.024.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.32 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1933; UP056.001.024.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.84 Megabytes (Box 24)
    [All Around Club] Sponsors musicals.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1933; UP056.001.024.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.33 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1933; UP056.001.024.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.29 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1933; UP056.001.024.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.36 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 5, 1933; UP056.001.024.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.30 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1933; UP056.001.024.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.41 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 19, 1933; UP056.001.024.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.42 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1933; UP056.001.024.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.04 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1933; UP056.001.024.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.65 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1933; UP056.001.024.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.29 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1933; UP056.001.024.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.47 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 24, 1933; UP056.001.024.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.84 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 31, 1933; UP056.001.024.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.27 Megabytes (Box 24)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 21, 1933; UP056.001.024.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.77 Megabytes (Box 24)
    Commencement Issue
  - Tufts Weekly, September 28, 1933; UP056.001.025.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.78 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1933; UP056.001.025.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.19 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 12, 1933; UP056.001.025.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.99 Megabytes (Box 25)
    Academic Honors p. 2.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1933; UP056.001.025.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.39 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1933; UP056.001.025.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.66 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1933; UP056.001.025.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.21 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1933; UP056.001.025.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.15 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 16, 1933; UP056.001.025.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.21 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 23, 1933; UP056.001.025.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.62 Megabytes (Box 25)
    Alumni association committees formed
  - Tufts Weekly, November 30, 1933; UP056.001.025.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.36 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1933; UP056.001.025.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.32 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1933; UP056.001.025.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.88 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 11, 1934; UP056.001.025.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.01 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 18, 1934; UP056.001.025.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.03 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 25, 1934; UP056.001.025.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.40 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1934; UP056.001.025.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.45 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 22, 1934; UP056.001.025.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.09 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1934; UP056.001.025.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.37 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1934; UP056.001.025.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.11 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1934; UP056.001.025.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.45 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1934; UP056.001.025.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.88 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 29, 1934; UP056.001.025.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.02 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, April Fool Issue, 1934; UP056.001.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 12, 1934; UP056.001.025.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.48 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 19, 1934; UP056.001.025.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.51 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1934; UP056.001.025.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.91 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1934; UP056.001.025.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.89 Megabytes (Box 25)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Prize Scholarship.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1934; UP056.001.025.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.60 Megabytes (Box 25)
    Lester R. Adelson, 1935.; [Alumni council] Newly formed
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1934; UP056.001.025.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.71 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 24, 1934; UP056.001.025.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.98 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 31, 1934; UP056.001.025.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.11 Megabytes (Box 25)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 21, 1934; UP056.001.025.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.47 Megabytes (Box 25)
    Commencement Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, September 27, 1934; UP056.001.026.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.37 Megabytes (Box 26)
    American association of college editors
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1934; UP056.001.026.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.39 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1934; UP056.001.026.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.12 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1934; UP056.001.026.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.56 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1934; UP056.001.026.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.38 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1934; UP056.001.026.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.35 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1934; UP056.001.026.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.37 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1934; UP056.001.026.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.30 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1934; UP056.001.026.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 18.82 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 29, 1934; UP056.001.026.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.87 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 6, 1934; UP056.001.026.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.16 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 13, 1934; UP056.001.026.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.57 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1935; UP056.001.026.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.52 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 17, 1935; UP056.001.026.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.75 Megabytes (Box 26)
    American association of college editors; [Administration] College exercises suspended one day preceding mid-year and final examination periods. p. 1.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 24, 1935; UP056.001.026.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.39 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1935; UP056.001.026.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.23 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1935; UP056.001.026.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.22 Megabytes (Box 26)
    [Alumnae Hall] Kaye MacKinnon gives dance recital for benefit of Alumnae Hall; American association of college editors
  - Tufts Weekly, February 28, 1935; UP056.001.026.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.53 Megabytes (Box 26)
    [Alumnae Hall] Kaye MacKinnon gives dance recital for benefit of Alumnae Hall
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1935; UP056.001.026.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.94 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1935; UP056.001.026.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.02 Megabytes (Box 26)
    [Alumnae Hall] Kaye MacKinnon gives dance recital for benefit of Alumnae Hall; Alumni questionaire indicates many relatives at Tufts
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1935; UP056.001.026.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.61 Megabytes (Box 26)
    American Institute of Electrical Engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, March 28, 1935 [April Fools Day], UP056.001.026.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.55 Megabytes (Box 26)
    April Fools Day insert.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1935; UP056.001.026.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.67 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 18, 1935; UP056.001.026.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.30 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 25, 1935; UP056.001.026.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.71 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 2, 1935; UP056.001.026.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.63 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1935; UP056.001.026.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.26 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1935; UP056.001.026.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.60 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 23, 1935; UP056.001.026.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.63 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 30, 1935; UP056.001.026.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.23 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 20, 1935; UP056.001.026.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.38 Megabytes (Box 26)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 26, 1935; UP056.001.027.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.85 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 3, 1935; UP056.001.027.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.17 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 10, 1935; UP056.001.027.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.47 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 17, 1935; UP056.001.027.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.07 Megabytes (Box 27)
    Academic Honors pp. 1,5.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 24, 1935; UP056.001.027.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.83 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 31, 1935; UP056.001.027.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.57 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 7, 1935; UP056.001.027.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.29 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 14, 1935; UP056.001.027.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.98 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1935; UP056.001.027.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.32 Megabytes (Box 27)
    Academic Honors p. 2. (editorial); [Alpha Omicron Pi] Fashion Show.